Austin Plambeck

(805) 405-3011 | austinplambeck2@gmail.com | https://plambo-world.netlify.app/

Summary

Multifaceted and dedicated professional with 5+ years' experience in project management, copywriting/editing, and editorial/publishing work. Expert at building long-lasting client relationships. Published author. Proficient web developer. B.S. in Environmental Science.

Skills

- Project Management
- Publishing/eBook Production
- > CMS, SDL, Oxygen, Rally

- Copywriting & CopyeditingSharePoint

> HTML, CSS, JavaScript

- Communication
- Microsoft Office/Google Suite GitHub

- > Building Relationships
- > Word, Excel, PowerPoint
- Canva/Adobe Photoshop

Work Experience

Editorial Assistant - EBSCO Information Services | February 2023 - PRESENT

- Streamlined editorial processes for a more efficient workflow involving contractors and editors
- Aided in achieving >95% currency for Dynamic Health Skills (our platform with the most traffic)
- Managed the entire editorial workflow and acted as a liaison between multiple parties
- Successfully utilized CMS to copyedit and update content on product
- Built strong relationships with contract writers, lasting for over two years

Author, Publisher, Creative Director - Tales of Storms Creative Studio | May 2022 - PRESENT

- Published eBooks and physical books on Amazon
- Responsible for typesetting, formatting, and design of eBooks and physical books
- Directed a marketing campaign utilizing SEO & Amazon Ads, increasing sales by 37%
- Head of copywriting, web design, social media, & graphic design

Front-End Web Developer | September 2021 - PRESENT

- Brought projects to life using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and GitHub
- Built these websites/web apps from the ground up:
 - Personal Portfolio (link)
 - The Film Generator (link)
 - Of the Sky: The Game [work in progress] (<u>link</u>)

Restoration Ecologist Intern - Green Kirkland Partnership | Sep. 2018 - June 2019

- Lead editor; managed the creation of all reports, maps, and figures
- Established efficient work plans, reaching goals while staying under budget by 52%
- Handled the logistics of large volunteer events and plant procurement and installation

Education

B.S., **Environmental Science** - University of Washington

• 3.50 GPA; Dean's List